imeetzu.com 2016-11-19

# iMeetzu - Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

For the sake of these Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy, the website located at www.iMeetzu.com is the same thing as "iMeetzu" or "iMeetzu.com". **By using iMeetzu.com you agree to _EVERYTHING_ set forth here on this page**, whether or not we say "by using iMeetzu you agree to" or something similar beforehand. 

**By using imeetzu you agree that you are at least 18 years old, and if you are not you will immediately cease and desist use of imeetzu.com and leave the website.**

By using iMeetzu you agree that iMeetzu owns anything you upload, post, tell us, inform us of, and so forth. This includes any pictures you upload, random comments you make, things you click on, feedback you fabulously provide (whether it's good or god awful), and so on. You agree that we may own and use all this awesome user-provided content as we see fit. However, we will not be divulging your emails to 3rd party peoples unless required to do so by law, so you don't have to worry about that, because frankly that's just lame and so not cool.

Furthermore, you agree not to upload or post any illegal content, copyrighted content you don't have the rights to, pornographic content (we don't want to see your genitals), or any other such obscene and utterly useless materials. In addition, you agree not to use iMeetzu in any way to spam or promote other websites, and agree that you will be held legally liable for any damages that should result to our user base or repuation, as well as be liable to us for any monetary gains you should yourself make, through such spamming/promotional efforts. This includes the use of bots, which are strictly FORBIDDEN.

Also, you agree that you will not hold us liable for any damages resulting from association with iMeetzu.com, affiliation with iMeetzu.com, use of iMeetzu.com, looking at iMeetzu.com, discussion of iMeetzu.com, and anything else you may happen to do that involves iMeetzu.com in any dynamic, situation, shape or form.

By using iMeetzu.com you also acknowledge/agree that we are in absolute total control of everything on iMeetzu, and we may cut you off from use of iMeetzu whenever we please, ban you whenever we please, delete your account whenever we please, delete any and everything you add/post/do on iMeetzu whenever we please, and do anything else we wish to regarding your account at any time without warning.

In terms of privacy, you agree that we may track information on you as necessary in order to display advertisements as we see fit and ensure our website functions as we see fit. This includes but is not limited to cookies for advertisements and cookies for allowing you to remain logged in to iMeetzu, among other things. We will not divulge personal contact information to the public or 3rd parties unless legally required to do so, but you must understand and agree that any personal contact information you post/upload is being divulged to whoever you are chatting with, or, in the case of your public profile (all profiles are public), to the entire internet. 

In addition, you agree that this website is governed by the laws of the state of Oregon in the United States of America and that any legal action on your and/or anyone else's behalf that involves iMeetzu.com will be filed and brought forth solely within the Polk County of the state of Oregon in the United States of America. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Lastly, you agree that we may change these terms of service and privacy policy whenever we want and however we want without giving you any notice. 

Feel free to contact us with any questions or suggestions you may have.
